Ewing Galloway Collection of Photographs
Ewing Galloway Collection of Photographs
- Human interest
  - A Portrait of a Musician Holding His Bow and Violin (86) (Oversize 11)
  - Children Getting Inoculated Against Scarlet Fever (89) (Oversize 11)
  - A Hobo Sewing Warm Clothes in His Woodland Home (91) (Oversize 11)
  - A Chemist in His Washington, D.C. Laboratory (93) (Oversize 11)
  - Father, Mother and Child (Family Pose Early 20th Century) (102) (Oversize 11)
  - Application For Naturalization Taken Under Oath (103) (Oversize 11)
  - Man Getting Oysters Out of the Water at the Oyster Beds in New Jersey (115) (Oversize 12)
  - Orphan Children's Outing Given by the Cleveland Automobile Club (116) (Oversize 12)
  - A Portrait of Mr. Munson Havens the Secretary of the Chamber of Commerce of Cleveland, Ohio (119) (Oversize 12)
  - An Employees Cooperative Store in Detroit, Michigan (123) (Oversize 12)
  - A Group of Veteran Gold Miners (130) (Oversize 12)
  - A Cardiac Class For Women Suffering From Cardiac Disease in New York City (140) (Oversize 12)
  - Postman Delivering Mail, His Uniform of Fifty Years or More Are Still Being Utilized (149) (Oversize 12)
  - Free Public Tennis Courts Located in Cleveland, Ohio (158) (Oversize 12)
  - A Protest Against Non-Employment and Discrimination Against Minorities (160) (Oversize 12)
  - A Concrete Bridge Over a Niagra River Above Niagra Falls, New York (174) (Oversize 12)
  - The Old Style, Free Delivery Postman with Horse and Buggy (186) (Oversize 12)
  - Excavating in Quest of Archeological Finds (191) (Oversize 12)
  - A View of a Guard Manning the Tower Overlooking the Sing Sing Prison in New York State (194) (Oversize 12)
- Unnumbered later additions
  - Postcard with photograph of City Hall in New York (Oversize 1)
    Gift of Margaret Fox, 2015.
  - Miscellaneous, 9 items (Oversize 1)
    Gift of the Ricker Library of Architecture and Art, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign, 2010.
    Places and subjects include New York City, Kansas City, St. Gudula Cathedral in Brussels, Niagara Falls, New York Harbor, a full-rigger "tall ship," turtle fishing in Abyssinia, and a Bagobo youth in the Philippines. Dates are unknown. All photos are 8x10" black and white originals.